# JORGE WOLFF

# IT SYSTEMS CONSULTANT



+240-793-9353



wesnetwork@keybyme.com



2 10413 Ridge Landing Pl., Damascus

I am skilled, experienced IT consultant that is self-motivated with a background in software and information technology systems. Apart from being talented with networks, I am just as dedicated to delivering the service needed for any company to succeed.

## EXPERIENCE

DINING ROOM SUPERVISOR | IT 2016 - Present | Five Star Residents

- Manage a team of front-of-house staff including scheduling, training, and general supervision.
- Providing excellent customer service to guests
- · Oversees the IT department to help manage network, wireless infrastructure, and applications.
- IT SYSTEMS CONSULTANT 2012 - 2016 | WES Networking
- Analyzing a company's IT system and infrastructure.
- · Diagnosing IT system problems, inefficiencies, and weaknesses
- Implementing a technological solution to meet business

SOFTWARE ENGINEER 2009 - 2012 | World Bank

- Provide ongoing maintenance, support, and enhancements in existing systems and platforms
- Test software development methodology in an agile environment.
- Work alongside other engineers on the team to elevate technology and consistently apply best practices.

# EDUCATION

1984 - 1988

UNITECH UNIVERSITY **Bachelor of Science, Computer Science** 

## SKILLS

- Database Management
- Design Thinking
- managing IT budgets
- Front End Coding
- Systems Consulting
- Problem-Solving
- Computer Literacy
- Project Management Tools
- Strong Communication

#### CERTIFICATES

• DBA & Audit System